hiyo.com 2012-05-06

# HiYo - Privacy Policy

FULL PRIVACY POLICY  
This statement applies to IncrediMail Ltd.'s ("IncrediMail") information collection and use policies with respect to use of the site currently located at www.HiYo.com (the "Site"), the HiYo instant messaging enhanced media content service ("The Service" or "HiYo"), and the software enabling the use thereof ("the Software"). By using this Site, Software and/or Service you consent to the data practices described in this Statement. Defined terms that are contained herein that are not accompanied by a definition, shall have the definition ascribed to them in the Terms and Conditions of Use of HiYo, the Software and the Site. 

THE SITE  
We do not request nor collect any personal information from Users who simply visit the Site. 

THE SERVICE   
The Service allows Users to add to their instant messages Enhanced Media Content (such as emoticons, enhanced text, sounds, winks, images and buzzes) (the "HiYo Content"). The Service also provides Users with Contextual Content Suggestions that may appear once a User writes certain text while conversing with another User through the Instant Messaging Application, in addition to certain enhanced content search options. While providing Contextual Content Suggestions we do not view nor access your conversations in any manner. In order to view HiYo Content the recipient of your instant message must also have the Software installed on his or her computer. A recipient of your instant message that contains HiYo Content that does not have the Software installed will receive an automatic message instructing him how to download the Software in order to view the HiYo Content sent by you. 

Service Registration Information and our use of your Personal Information When you install the Software you will not be required to provide us with information. The Software will create on your computer a unique identifier, based on your personal settings in the Instant Messaging Application, and shall send only such identifier to IncrediMail's servers. Your personal settings in the Instant Messaging Application will not be viewed nor accessed by IncrediMail nor can they be reproduced from the unique identifier by IncrediMail in any manner. 

Customer support forms IncrediMail may post from time to time customer support forms. These forms may ask for personally and non-personally identifiable information including but not limited to license registration information, purchase information and a valid email address. This information will be used solely for the purpose of providing efficient customer support. 

Non- Personally Identifiable Information IncrediMail will use certain non-personally identifiable information of Users to create aggregate, non-personal, demographic reports about the Users of the Service. 

GENERAL USAGE PATTERNS  
IncrediMail may gather information related generally to Users' use of the Software, Service, and Site to create aggregate, non-personal reports and statistics about Users' usage of the Service and the HiYo Content. 

This information, which will only be collected and maintained in aggregate, anonymous form, will be used to, among other things: Provide IncrediMail with a better understanding of how Users use the Service and the various features thereof; Help IncrediMail to create and provide new services and offerings to Users; and Conduct and publish aggregate, anonymous, market research results. 

PERMITION TO UTILIZE  
In order to receive the benefits provided by the Software, you herby grant permission for IncrediMail to utilize the processor and bandwidth of your computer 

COMPUTER SETTINGS  
IncrediMail may collect settings, technical and other information from Users' computers, such as a computer's operating system, IncrediMail and browser versions used, connectivity, various communication parameters and other information related to the operation and interaction of the Software, subject to the provisions herein. This information will neither contain nor be linked to any personally identifiable information. 

COOKIES   
"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Service and Web Site. IncrediMail may use cookies to save certain information about a User and others who visit the HiYo Web Site, in order to facilitate and enhance future activities with the Service and/or Web Site. IncrediMail does not use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to the Service. IncrediMail currently contracts with several online partners to help manage and optimize its Internet business and communications. IncrediMail uses the services of a marketing company to help it measure the effectiveness of its advertising and how visitors use this Site. To do this, IncrediMail uses Web beacons and cookies provided by IncrediMail's marketing company on the Site. The type of information IncrediMail collects includes the pages visited, the product codes and prices that visitors purchase and coupons that were used during purchase. By supplementing IncrediMail's records, this information helps IncrediMail learn things like what pages are most attractive to visitors of the Site, which of IncrediMail's products most interest its customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although IncrediMail's marketing company manages the information coming from the Site on behalf of IncrediMail, IncrediMail controls how that data may and may not be used. We may use an outside advertising company to display advertisements on the Site and Service. These ads may contain cookies. The advertisement company may collect cookies received with outside ad banners. We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the advertising company. 

IP ADDRESSES  
An Internet Protocol address is a number that's automatically assigned to a computer when using the Internet. Web servers can automatically identify individual computers by their IP address. IncrediMail may collect IP addresses to: 

Facilitate system administration; Diagnose system problems; Report aggregate User information; and Avoid hacking attacks on the IncrediMail server. 

IncrediMail does not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information, even if such information is voluntarily provided by a User. 

CONSENT TO PROCESSING  
Users, including without limitation, Users in the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of their personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information, to the extant that such information is being collected, in the United States. 

LEGAL DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION  
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Agreement, IncrediMail shall, pursuant to valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order, allow access to all available and relevant information, including Users' IP addresses, in order to comply with such valid legal process and to otherwise protect IncrediMail's rights and property. If warranted, IncrediMail may also allow access to this information in special emergencies where physical safety is at risk. 

SECURITY  
While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personally identifiable information, to the extent that such information is in our possession. 

OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS  
The Site and/or Service may contain links to other Web sites. IncrediMail is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. All questions concerning the IncrediMail Privacy Policy should be directed [here](mailto:privacy@hiyo.com). 

CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT  
IncrediMail may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and at any time, with or without a release of a new version of the Software, and without actual notice to you. When we do, we will also revise the "Effective Date" of the Privacy Statement. All such changes to this Privacy Policy will appear on the Site. IncrediMail may provide additional notice of such changes by providing a link from the Service to the Site. You agree that your continuing to use the Software, Service and/or Site for a period of thirty (30) days after such notice has been posted on the Site for the first time shall constitute your consent to the new or revised Privacy Policy. 

RISKS  
THE SOFTWARE, SERVICE AND SITE MAY BE VULNERABLE TO VARIOUS SECURITY ISSUES AND SHOULD NOT BE CONSIDERED SECURE. BY USING THE SOFTWARE, SERVICE AND SITE YOU MAY BE SUBJECT TO VARIOUS RISKS, INCLUDING AMONG OTHERS: Unauthorized exposure of information and material you post on or through the Service. Exposure to objectionable material and/or parties, including without limitation, content and messages that may offend and which may contain contaminated files. Unauthorized invasion of your privacy during, or as a result of, your or another's use of the Service. Spoofing, eavesdropping, sniffing, spamming, breaking passwords, harassment, fraud, forgery, "imposturing", electronic trespassing, tampering, hacking, nuking, system contamination including without limitation use of viruses, worms and Trojan horses causing unauthorized, damaging or harmful access and/or retrieval of information and data on your computer and other forms of activity that may even be unlawful. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE SUBJECTED TO THESE RISKS, YOU ARE ADVISED NOT TO USE THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICE. 

All questions concerning the IncrediMail Privacy Policy should be directed [here](mailto:privacy@hiyo.com).

Effective Date: July 1st 2007.
